[crowd cheering]
Rob! I love you!
Oh, Rob!
Hmm.
[chuckles]
Oh, hello there, handsome.
Muah! [blows kiss]
I hope my fans love your new loo
as much as I do.
-[zapping]
-[gasps]
Hi, Rob.
Hey! Huh?
[crowd cheering wildly]
Okay, everyone, put your hands t
and get ready to make some noise
for Rob Heartthrob!
Oh, Rob!
[crowd chanting] We want Rob! We
We want Rob! We want Rob!
[squealing]
Oh, Rob!
[gasping]
-[screams]
-[girl] Where did he go?
Fabulous.
Huh?
[tires screech]
[gasps] Oh! [giggles]
Wow!
-[ringing]
-Come on, sweetie, let's go for
[barking]
Um, excuse me. I'm new in town.
I was wondering
if your gym offers Pilates class
-For who, your granny? [snickers
-Uh...
Sweetie, this gym only offers th
in cutting-edge training regimen
-Oh!
-Submersive Hydrocycling...
Ugh.
...Zero Grav Power Lifting.
[straining]
[grunting]
[gasps]
[laughs sheepishly]
Wow. They sure take their workou
seriously around here.
[gasps] Cool, a bookstore.
I can get all the reading materi
for my new school.
[bell tinkles]
Hmm.
Uh...
Pardon me, can you tell me
where you keep your books?
Oh, we don't carry books anymore
They scare the customers away.
You know, print is so last-centu
But we do have
these 24-karat gold bookmarks,
pure silk, runway-ready bookbags
and, of course,
our five-star gourmet reading ca
[giggles]
Whoa! [gasps] No way.
Yves Mont Blanc's latest boots!
They so didn't carry those in my
I have to have 'em.
Huh?
Excuse me, do you have them
in a six-and-a-half?
All you need to know is that
they're too expensive for you.
That is, like, so rude. And so c
I just love Beverly Hills.
[computer] Assets will reach tar
in T-minus ten seconds.
[Jerry] Cluck, cluck.
The chickens have left the roost
I repeat:
the chickens have left the roost
Time to put Operation Sushi Roll
into effect.
Are you completely sure about th
Sure as tea time is four p.m.
[computer] Activate chain of com
[alarm blaring]
Oops. Sorry.
It's okay.
[all scream]
Huh?
[all sigh]
[gasping]
[squeals]
[grunts] Oh, no! My bags!
[all screaming]
[people screaming]
[pig squeals]
We are so lucky
we didn't just get pummeled.
[Clover] No doubt.
[people screaming]
Oh, no! Even the sushi has attit
in Beverly Hills.
Well, maybe it's just trying
to get back to the ocean.
Apparently the ocean's this way.
Run for it.
[screaming]
Whoa!
We're not the only ones in troub
Check out that poor little piggy
-[snorting]
-Come on.
We've gotta stop this thing
before it turns all four of us i
Hmm?
Okay, we're gonna need
a long piece of rope.
Hmm.
-Here. My belt.
-Good.
Now we just have to figure out
how to hook one end onto the rol
and the other end under that arc
Well, I can handle the archway.
Yeah, no probs.
[grunts]
Whoa, killer move.
Time to bail.
Hi-yah!
[grunts]
-[squealing]
-[gasps]
-[horn honking]
-[snorts]
[grunts]
And not a moment too soon. [gigg
Wow. That was a really close cal
Totally.
Yeah. Um...
I guess after that bizarro exper
we should probably introduce our
Um, I'm Sam.
Hi, I'm Alex.
And you guys rocked back there.
Thanks. I'm Clover.
And aside from the major drama
we just went through,
it's a total pleasure to meet yo
Yeah. You know, we could go and
a ginger/avocado milkshake
to forget about our emotions.
-Okay.
-Sounds good.
[all] Yeah.
Very well, then.
[Clover] Oops, almost forgot.
Accessories like these
don't grow on trees.
[car horn plays "La Cucaracha"]
[music blaring on car stereo]
Hello! I am not getting
any younger, losers.
That's more like it.
You, wash and wax my whip.
Yes, Mandy. Right away.
And I don't wanna see any streak
when I look at my reflection in
-[whimpers]
-Whoa.
You, rotate my rims, defog my mi
and fluff my seat cushion. Pront
Anything you say, Mandy.
You, fill 'er up. And don't use
any of that cheapo gas either.
What can I do for you, Mandy?
[gasps] You can take a big step
I have a polka-dot-on-stripe
restraining order
which you have clearly just viol
-[laughter]
-[car sensor chirps]
[ringing]
[boy] All right, so, like,
welcome to Bev High, everyone.
So, what's on the agenda
for the first day of school, Man
Trample the football captain's h
Shake down the geek squad
for homework assignments?
Put those on my schedule for lat
Right now,
I've got something else in mind.
[boy] All new students
need to totally report
to the principal's office, lik,
-Sorry.
-Hmm.
Hmm.
[running footsteps]
-Um... [gulps]
-[running footsteps]
-[all grunt, squeal]
-Excuse me.
-Alex? Clover?
-Huh?
What are you guys doing here?
-I go here.
-[squealing]
-[thud]
-[grunting]
-I just transferred.
-Awesome. Me too.
Me three.
Okay, not to get all horoscopy,
isn't this like the biggest
cosmic coincidence of the centur
Totally. It's almost like we wer
meant to hang out together.
-[Mrs. Scritch clears throat]
-[gasps]
[Alex] Uh-oh.
I don't suppose you ladies
could break away from your frate
to meet your new principal?
Ooh! You must be Mrs. Scritch.
My name is Sam.
And I just wanted you to know th
in anticipation of my classes,
I've gone on a few field trips,
written a term paper
and done some advance summer rea
Wow, Sam. Prepared much?
Yeah. You must be, like,
a big-time brainiac.
Well, that's all very interestin
But this school does not look fa
upon grade-grubbers.
-Huh? But I wasn't--
-And...
just because you're new here doe
you'll get any special treatment
I'll be watching you.
Hmm.
Enjoy your time at Beverly High.
-[indistinct chatter]
-[laughter]
[whooping]
Oh, hey!
Is it me, or is Mrs. Scritch a r
Let's just say
she's about as friendly as a jai
[all giggle]
Well, I hope some of the other B
are nicer than she is.
Hola,newbies.
I am Mandy,
In-Crowd Ambassadrice of Bev Hig
[all snicker]
I insist you let me buy you
a first-day double-soy-chai
-at the in-school latte bar.
-Sure thing.
-Thanks.
-Sounds great.
Hmm.
I can't believe
we've only been here ten minutes
and we're already in the in-crow
I hope you ladies like extra foa
My middle name is foam.
In that case...
[all] Huh?
Mmm.
[screaming]
[laughter]
Welcome to Bev High, losers. [ca
[crowd laughing]
Okay, it's official.
I'm completely humiliated.
Luckily we have each other.
You guys are, like, my total NBG
NBGFs?
New best girlfriends. [chuckles]
Oh! I feel the same way.
So do I. Which is why
I vote we stick together.
[all] Oh! [giggling]
Uh, Sam, when you said "stick to
I didn't think you meant literal
[all grunting]
[laughing]
I guess that double-soy-chai
really thrashed our threads.
No worries. I'm totally prepped
for such an unfortunate sitch.
Hmm.
I have at least ten back-up outf
stashed in my locker.
Ten outfits?
Now that's what I call resourcef
Yeah, Clover. You're, like,
a one-woman wardrobe department.
But before we change,
shouldn't we do something about
Oh, we'll deal with her later,
when she, like, least expects it
-[Alex giggles]
-[Sam] Oh.
-[rumbling]
-[all gasp]
Whoa! Either that coffee just se
into my central nervous system,
or we're having a major earthqua
Or maybe it's another one
of Mandy's evil tricks.
[all grunting]
Quick, girls. Form a human chain
Hey, what do you know? My plan w
Whoa!
[all yelling]
Hmm.
[grunts]
[coughing]
[screaming]
Okay, nobody panic.
[grunting]
Whoa. What is this place?
I don't know, but is anyone else
a serious alien vibe?
I doubt it has anything to do
with ETs, Alex.
Whatever the vibe is,
it's definitely spooky.
[gasps] Wait a sec.
I bet we're on some reality TV p
This is LA, after all.
[gasps] I'm so not camera-ready.
[giggles]
[Tad] I'm not so sure these girl
what it takes to be spies, Jerry
I agree they're a bit rough
around the edges,
but I assure you they're WOOHP-w
Our tests confirm that they each
the spy gene.
The only genes these girls appea
are designer jeans.
Nonetheless, their typical schoo
profile is the perfect cover.
The Sweat-Sensor Lie Detector?
The Human Memory Eraser?
GLOSSS: Global Satellite
Surveillance System?
I don't know, girls.
I get the feeling this place is
Whoa. Check this out.
Huh? What's the 911, Sammy?
Yeah, what's so exciting about
a bunch of boring office supplie
[whirring]
Huh? [gasping]
Whoa.
[all] Hey! [gasping]
[screaming]
Rough around the edges? More lik
[Jerry] Nothing a little trainin
won't fix.
-[zapping continues]
-[girls screaming]
[all yelling]
-Hmm.
-[alarm blaring]
[gasping]
[all] Oh!
[screaming]
I told you we were abducted by a
Actually, the aliens
are down in the freezer.
[screaming]
-[Jerry clears throat]
-[gasping]
-We're agents.
-Hi, girls.
[gasps]
And totally cute ones at that.
[squeals]
Oh, I wish I'd remembered my hea
We're not talent agents.
We're secret agents.
I'm Jerry and this is Tad.
Welcome to WOOHP, girls.
Hmm? [laughing]
Huh?
I don't care who you are.
I demand to know
why we've been brought here.
And I demand to know what a WOOH
-[snaps fingers]
-[all gasp] Huh?
WOOHP stands for
World Organization Of Human Prot
a top-secret institute
aimed at fighting global crime.
You're here because you've been
to join our elite group
of international spies.
C'ha, right.
Just 'cause we live in Beverly H
doesn't mean we're stupid.
Very true, Clover.
After monitoring you,
Sam and Alex for years,
I've determined that you have
quite an aptitude for espionage.
[grunting]
[giggles]
Oh.
Hmm.
Ha! Hi-yah!
[all gasp]
-[grunts]
-[all cheering]
And so, not only did I arrange f
to be transferred to Bev High,
but I also arranged the "sushi t
you took earlier.
During which, I must say, you di
a tremendous amount of potential
Ugh! You monitored us? Hello, cr
Okay. That's it. I'm calling the
-If you ladies do not wish to e
-[all scream]
...you don't have to.
Oh, that's good. 'Cause we so do
Yeah. Moving to a new city
is stressy enough.
The whole extracurricular spy i
just doesn't fit into my schedl
-Hmm.
-Um...
Yeah, speaking of schedules,
we really need to be
getting back to school.
I understand. Hmm.
But before I let you go,
I have something for you.
It's a WOOHP wallet phone.
If you happen to have a change o
you can use it to contact Jerry.
-[all groan]
-[Jerry] One more thing.
Under no condition are you to me
what you've seen or heard here t
Or what, you'll have us eliminat
[laughs]
[chuckles] Of course not.
We stopped doing that in the '90
We'll have you one-way teleporte
to Siberia.
-[all gasp]
-Ta-ta.
[screaming]
[gasps]
[grunting]
-[all laughing]
-Hello, losers.
[laughter]
-[gasps] Samantha!
-Oh...
What in the world are you doing
inside that trash can?
Uh... nothing, Mrs. Scritch.
Just, uh, trying to tidy up the
As I told you before,
your pathetic attempts
to score points with me
will not get you ahead at Beverl
Now get to class.
[all murmuring]
[rings]
Bye, girls. See you tomorrow.
-Come on, girls, let's go to the
-[engine starts]
[laughing]
Pick up the pace, ladies.
We're wasting prime shoppage tim
[laughs]
Aw, don't tell me
they're closing the mall early t
I haven't even broken a sweat.
[woman on TV]
Do you desire a superior look?
Do you crave the genetically ua
Do you long for others to snip
-behind your back out of sheere
-Hey!
Yes, yes, and hecka yes!
Then the Fabulizer is the procs
Uh...
Observe the elevated moisture o
with reduced blink intervals
for optimum sparkle,
the perfectly arched right eyer
custom engineered
to a sumptuous 47.2 degree ange
the dual-action dimples
with optional cleft chin,
the ultra-white perma-smile
fortified with 15% extra teeth,
the platinum-streaked hair
that delicately covers one eye
for that mysterious peek-a-booa
And, finally,
the attention-grabbing cheek ml
Now available in three colors.
With a visit to one of our
diamond-studded, velvet-lined o
and three easy payments of onl
this fabulous look can be your.
[all murmuring]
[crowd gasps]
Outta my way! I demand to be Fab
right this instant.
[screams]
[clamoring]
Ist all working perfectly.
Soon they vill all belong
to Your Fabulous-ness.
[evil laugh]
[birds chirping]
Where am I?
What is this place?
[evil laugh] You can't run away.
You will be spies... spies... sp
You are working for me, working
Spies... spies... spies... spies
[screaming]
[groans] What a nightmare! [exha
[computer] Your system has been
-by the WOOHP virus.
-Huh?
Shut down immediately.
[gasps] The WOOHP virus?
[grunts]
[screaming]
[alarm beeping]
No way. Episode two was way bett
than episode one.
-Episode two--
-[gasps]
[grunts]
-[wind whistling]
-[gasps]
Hey, wait! There must be some mi
I live in Beverly Hills, not the
Not anymore.
WOOHP has officially relocated y
[sighs] Whoa!
[indistinct chatter]
I'll have the jicama kumquat
power smoothie with a soy protei
Sorry, your card's been declined
Declined? But I just paid my bil
Here, try one of these.
Oh!
[buzzer]
But... that's impossible.
They can't all be maxed out. [ga
Put your hands in the air
and step away from the plastic.
Whoa! [screams]
-[door shuts]
-This is totally unfair.
Prison stripes
are so not matching my shoes.
W-shaped handcuffs?
[gasps] Now I know who's to blam
for this bogus mall incarceratio
Sam, it's Clover.
You're never gonna believe
what just happened.
Whatever it is, it can't be wors
than being attacked by a compute
Oh, yeah?
Try a round of tumbleweed wrestl
Whoa!
That's it!
It's time to call that jerky Jer
and give him a piece of our mind
Hello, Clover. So lovely to her
Hey, mister. Save what you're se
for someone who's buyin'.
Yeah. We know what you
and your sneaky organization are
making our lives miserable
so we'll be spies for you.
I have no idea what you're talki
It's against WOOHP policy
to interfere with civilians' liv
Regardless, I'd be happy to help
out of your current situations.
Provided you help me as well.
-[chimes]
-I can't believe it.
We're being blackmailed by a bal
That's "balding."
And trust me,
you won't regret your decision.
Decision? What decision?
[screaming]
[gasps]
Right now, it's time to start
your official WOOHP training.
This is so bogus.
You're actually forcing us to be
Exactly what kind of training
are we talking about?
Over the next 48 hours,
you'll be instructed
in extreme martial arts,
high-tech weapon and equipment u
and super-secret surveillance te
In short, it's going to be chall
grueling and extremely demanding
So... what's the upside?
Well, we do get to see Tad
in a flight suit. [chuckles]
Oh!
Speaking of suits...
[all squealing]
[gasping]
Here are your spy uniforMrs.
Now let's begin, shall we?
[screaming]
[siren wailing]
-Whoa!
-Alex!
I'm okay. [laughs sheepishly]
No.
Hey, girls, I think I see someth
Huh?
-Oh.
-[all] Huh?
[Clover] Oh!
Ooh, handbags!
Oh, my. No.
[sighs]
-Huh?
-[all grunting]
[gasps, groans]
Zut alors!
Wow, this place is amazing.
Hmm. Time to focus, ladies.
I'm going to show you a fool-pro
WOOHP kata called Blender of Dea
Observe the five lethal speeds.
-Chop! Crush! Grind! Liquefy!
-[all gasp]
Hi-yah!
Puree! Hyah!
Okay, now you show me Blender of
Hey, this is kinda fun.
Bring on the baddies, Jer. Hyah!
And the tropical fruit.
[gasping]
[grunting]
Ooh! [giggles]
Hmm.
[all gasp]
[all] Chop! Crush! Grind!
Hi-yah!
[all] Yeah! [gasp]
Yah! Yah! Yah!
[grunting]
[whistles]
Anyone know the kata for "run?"
[all scream]
[chuckles]
[gasping]
We can't outblast, outfight
or outrun this thing. What do we
We outsmart it. Follow me.
Hey, grease breath, over here.
Let 'er rip!
Incoming! Ha!
Whoa!
-All right!
-[all] Yeah!
How's our success rate looking n
Most impressive.
Perhaps you can be spies after a
That is, if you're willing to wo
on the rest of your skills in th
-[all] Yeah!
-Consider it done.
Then consider yourselves WOOHP a
Here are your ID cards.
-No way.
-[squealing]
[device beeping]
-Duty calls.
-Huh?
Well, tell it to call back later
We've been up all night.
Sorry. Spy missions wait for no
[all sigh]
Being a spy is so cool.
I always wanted to take a sea cr
-Me too.
-Oh, me three.
Congratulations on your training
spies.
It's gonna be a pleasure working
Oh, the pleasure's all mine.
[Jerry clears throat]
Are there any WOOHP rules
against inter-office romance, Je
[sighs] Now for the mission,
there has been a number
of mysterious disappearances
in the greater Los Angeles area,
one of them being
rock star Rob Heartthrob.
[gasps] Rob Heartthrob?
Oh, he's only, like,
my special celeb soulmate.
[sobbing] I get all misty
just thinking about his songs.
Well, save the sobbing,
because you'll be exploring
a missing celebrity of a differe
Peppy Wolfman.
Like I've said before,
"A peppy pet is a happy pet."
Hey, I've heard all about this g
He's a pet motivational speaker.
He specializes in cheering up an
of the rich and famous.
Or at least he was up until yest
before vanishing
from his Beverly Hills office.
We want you to investigate and s
if the disappearances are relate
And now for a spy's best friend:
the gadgets.
We have the Fountain Pen Microph
the Monocle Magnifier,
and my favorite,
the Ascending Ascot Cable.
[clears throat] Jer, if we're go
this whole spy thingy,
we're gonna have to do it with s
I took the liberty of whipping u
a few new designs.
Hmm. I'm not sure.
[Clover] Okay.
Oh, my.
Oh!
No, no, no, I don't think so.
-[Clover] Ooh!
-[Jerry] Um...
Oh, now that's more like it.
Very well, then.
[beeping]
Whoa! [all gasp]
Wow!
[laughing]
-Awesome!
-Yeah.
Now for your new,
albeit unorthodox, gadgets.
The Compowder,
a communication device/supercomp
discreetly concealed
in the shape of a make-up compac
the Expandable Cable Bungee Belt
the Laser Lipstick...
Aah!
-Oopsie.
-[Jerry clears throat]
...the Ever-expanding Bubble Gum
the Suction Cup Bottom,
Drill Heel Go-Go Boots...
Oh, très Euro chic.
...the Heat Sensor 6000
Infrared Motion-Detector Sunglas
-Wow, coolio.
-Yeah.
...the Molecular Separating Perf
the Tornado-In-A-Can-Of-Hairspra
Awesome.
...the Superfoaming Pomade Grena
and, of course, the Jetpack back
So, Jerry, where's our super coo
personal transport device
to get us to Peppy's office?
Just leave that to me.
[screaming] Jerry!
[screaming]
Huh?
[cat meows]
[wailing]
Hmm.
Okay, spy sisters, it's mission
[laughs]
[grunting]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Time out
Don't you think we should try to
a little less like teen spies?
[grunts] Ha!
Disguises are a great idea, Samm
Only, how does this Compowder ev
Only one way to find out.
Hmm. [gasps]
Oh. Ah!
[screaming] Ew, nast!
[clucking]
Oh, now that's more my speed.
-[Sam] Wow.
-[Alex laughs]
[giggling]
Voilà!The perfect Beverly Hill
All we need now is a pet.
[Alex whistles]
-[squeals]
-[giggling]
Pee-ew! What are you still doing
with that thing, Alex?
-It's not a thing. It's Oinky.
-[snorting]
Well, not exactly what I had in
but I guess he'll do in a pinch.
-[meowing]
-[snorting]
-[chirping]
-[barking]
It's scandalous!
Mr. Wolfman isn't seeing
any of his animal clients today.
I'm gonna have to ask you all to
But I have to see Peppy this ins
Crackers is so depressed
he hasn't spoken to me in days.
If we're going to figure out
what happened to Peppy,
we have to get past that recepti
Then we're gonna need
a five-alarm diversion.
Hey, Alex, why don't you
put that pig to good use?
-Okay, Oinky, wanna be a deputy
-[snorts]
Go hog wild for Mommy.
[squealing]
[barking]
Oh!
-Hey, get back here!
-[cat meows]
[grunts]
[crowd panicking]
[snarling]
[barking]
[snorting]
[straining] It's locked.
Luckily, I've got just the key
to get us in.
[squeals]
Whoa! Hey, who's getting
all gropey with my bag?
Let's see. If I were a clue,
where would I hide?
Hmm.
Like, hello? What's this thing?
Man, this spying stuff
is a lot harder than I thought.
Hmm.
If only WOOHP had a time machine
we could travel back to yesterda
and see what happened to Peppy i
Maybe we can.
Come on, gimme a boost.
[yells]
If I can hack into the surveilla
with our Compowder,
maybe we can see what happened y
Sorry. Wrong plug.
[laughs sheepishly]
-Huh?
-[powers up]
Ah.
There he is,
just like in the photo Jerry sho
Except, is it possible
he got even hairier?
Oh, how dare he walk away!
Doesn't he know
we're trying to spy on him?
Let's fast-forward
and see if he comes back.
[Clover laughs]
Who's that overly-processed,
cosmetic-counter disaster?
I think it might actually be Pep
Why does he look so different?
Hey, what's that in his hand?
I don't know.
It looks like some sort of recei
And check out the weird symbol o
Wonder what it stands for. Hmm.
[receptionist] You celebs think
you can go anywhere you please.
Now let me in,
or I'll break the door down!
It's the receptionist
and she's majorly chaffed.
[grunting] Peppy is not gonna be
very happy about this.
Where'd they go?
-[elephant trumpets]
-[gasps]
[growls angrily]
Good thinkin', Alex.
These Suction-Cup Bottom Go-Go B
are da bomb.
Ooh, fashionable and functional.
[all grunting]
Besides that one bad hair moment
I'd say our first mission was wa
-[clamoring]
-[blows landing]
Rude much?
Don't they know there's a totall
spy sesh goin' down here?
Uh, no, Clover. That's kinda the
[crowd clamoring]
Come on, girls.
Let me in. Let me in.
[all] Hmm.
[indistinct chatter]
[snorting]
Ooh! Maybe they're some kind
of nouveau tanning beds.
Whoa, what are those things?
Whatever they are,
they've got the same weird symbo
we saw on the receipt Peppy was
Hey, you're right, Sammy.
[woman on TV] Do you crave cool?
Do you long to be more populara
Do you desire the joy of beinga
over the pain of being a two?
[sighing]
Then the Fabulizer is the procs
[all cheering]
[gasps]
Hmm.
[snorting]
[crowd gasps]
[laughs]
[crowd exclaims]
[all] Fabulous!
[laughing]
I don't know what's weirder,
the way they look,
or the fact that they all seem t
Now we know why Peppy looked so
He must've gone out
and gotten this gnarly treatment
-[Compowder ringing]
-Hmm?
Hello, girls. How's the missio
Freaky.
On account of before he went mis
the Pepster was Fabulized.
Fabulized?
Put through a trendy machine
for insecure people
and given a majorly unoriginal l
Though I'm extremely disturbed b
that someone would actually
employ a machine to alter their
I must say you three have done
excellent spy work.
Wouldn't you agree, Tad?
Absolutely, Jerry.
Their findings are... most inter
What's even more interesting is,
we're totally beginning
to dig the spy life.
[giggles] So if you ever want
to get together over a latte
-or swap spy stories...
-Hmm.
...I'm so there.
-[chimes]
[gasps]
Oh, no! We're late for school.
On the contrary.
WOOHP has high-tech holograms
standing in for you.
No one will even notice you'rem
Oh, yeah, real stealthy.
No one'll notice a thing.
As in we really need to get back
to Bev High ASAP, or we're dead
I'll send the WOOHP jet right aw
Whoa!
Coolio! When you say right away,
you mean right away.
And, since you have a trigonomt
this afternoon,
I've taken the liberty of pickn
the foremost authority on the u
to get you up to speed
on your way to class.
-Thanks for covering our backs,
-[gasps]
Wait, I forgot Oinky.
Don't worry, Alex. I'll send a
to retrieve him. Cheerio.
Whoa!
Boss, we've got a problem.
[Fabu] Hmm.
Then I suggest you take care of
[laughs]
-[snarls]
-Ow!
Hmm.
So, let me get this straight.
The square of the length of the
opposite the right angle,
which we call the hypotenuse,
is equal to the sum of the squar
of the lengths of the two other
Mmm. Couldn't have said it
better myself, Samantha.
-[thud]
-Whoa!
-[rapid beeping]
-What was that?
We've just been hit by something
[screaming]
Whoa, check out that ship.
It's, like, all sorts of mega-mo
Try mega-Martian.
I told you aliens had something
to do with this.
Looks like auto-pilot time's ove
We're gonna have to do
some defensive driving, and quic
Well, luckily, I got my permit l
[grunts]
Whoa!
[screaming]
[Yuri snickers]
[rapid beeping]
-[Sam] Whoa!
-[Clover screaming]
[screaming]
[gasping]
Oopsie. My bad.
Don't worry, girls.
We'll be in striking position in
-[gasping]
-[screaming] Alex!
[grunting]
[grunts] Wow, this look is popul
Even aliens are getting it now.
Get off my ship!
Whoa!
[screaming]
Hang on, Alex. We're coming.
[Alex screaming]
[groans, sighs]
[screaming]
Doesn't this guy ever give up?
Apparently not.
I say we give him the slip.
He can't chase what he can't see
Yah!
[snickers]
Huh? What happened? Where are th
Oh!
Yeah! We did it!
Score one for the good spies.
Now let's get back to school.
[grunting]
-[rumbling]
-[Mrs. Scritch] Oh!
-Huh?
-[creaking]
Hmm.
We have the routine down.
Now all we gotta do
is learn how to land properly.
Mmm-hmm.
Careful, girls. The last thing I
is to get caught by Mrs. Scritch
[all scream]
♪ Walk like an Egyptian ♪
What are we gonna do now?
Scritch is right on our tail.
Not for long.
[gasps]
-Hyah!
-Awesome.
Hmm.
Well, well, well. What do we hav
[meows]
I'm sorry to report
that ze infiltrators got away, s
Really? Tell me more about these
Are they... dangerous?
Vell, sir, zey are not actually
professional spies.
Not professional spies? Interest
So what are they?
Zey are three teenage girls
from Beverly Hills.
[laughs] How fabulous.
And you let them get away?
Yes, sir, zey disappeared into t
Great shame for Yuri, sir.
It doesn't matter.
After tonight, we will be at ful
and Earth will no longer be
a concern for us.
Now hand me some more seaweed wr
-Whoa!
-[Fabu grunts]
Fine! Just drop it on me.
[laughs] Thanks to our tutor,
that test was a total breeze.
Yet another perk of our secret s
[giggles]
-[all laughing]
-[Alex] Whoa!
Everyone looks so different.
Yeah, in a freakishly
identical kind of way.
Ugh! I can't believe
they're all falling for that lam
[laughter]
Ha! Nice face, losers.
That look is, like, so yesterday
[Clover] This is the face I was
Whatever!
I'd still ask for a total refund
[all laugh]
Yeah, well, you may think
you're all that, Mandy,
but we're way cooler than you,
because we're undercover spi--
[muffled screams]
Clover, if you tell anyone our s
Jerry'll ship us off to Siberia.
Oh, it'd be worth the trip just
the look on Mandy's fake face.
[Jerry] Psst. Ladies, over here.
[giggles] Great costume, Jer.
Only, why are you wearing a hair
when you've got no hair?
I have some hair, Clover.
On the mission front,
I've been able to make some head
It turns out all of the missing
had the Fabulizer treatment
prior to vanishing.
What a coincidence.
The person who tried to take us
was also Fabulized.
Oh, my. Thank you, Sam,
for this information.
Girls, I think it's high time we
who's behind these Fabulizer mac
Ooh, that sounds like fun.
We can pick a Fabulized person
and tail 'em until they disappea
And I know just the person we ca
Mandy.
Ew! Couldn't we, like,
pick someone less repulsive?
[laughter]
A classmate is a perfect choice.
Mandy it is.
-[beeping]
-[gasps]
Duty calls. Kitchen duty, that i
I have cookies in the oven.
[all gasp]
You may think you've gotten away
with vandalizing the school, Sam
but I've got the goods on you.
Mmm.
I'll expect to see you in my off
first thing tomorrow morning
to receive your punishment.
And, trust me, it won't be a lig
I can't believe it.
I've never gotten in trouble
like this before.
Tragically unfashionable and a c
Guess they're letting anyone
into Bev High these days.
-[laughing]
-Grr!
[laughs]
[grunting]
[crowd laughing]
[giggles]
That must be Mandy's room.
Too bad we can't see what's goin
Let's see what the Heat Sensor 6
Sunglasses have to say about tha
Now, time to get some beauty sle
Not like I need it.
Hmm.
[moaning]
[snoring]
She's out cold.
Now's our chance to slip inside.
-[Compowder beeps]
-[all gasp]
[groans]
[faint beeping]
The Compowder's picking up
some sort of signal.
But it doesn't say where it's co
[Mandy groans]
[snoring]
[all gasp]
Okay, that was bizarre
even by Mandy standards.
[Sam] Come on.
Look! Over there.
Where did all these people
come from?
And where could they be going
at this time of night?
[Clover] Whatever Mandy's up to,
she seems to have started a new
-Whoa!
-[all gasp]
It's that crazy ship from before
Hit the deck.
Hold on. I don't think it's here
Huh?
Oh!
[all] Whoa!
Wow.
Fabulous! [cackles]
[sniffing]
[snorting]
[gasps] Oinky! What did they do
-I've gotta save him.
-Alex!
-[grunts]
-[Oinky squealing]
Hyah!
[screaming]
[all] Fabulous!
[all grunt]
Fabulous!
Just to be safe, we better try t
with the Fabulized people.
Do we have to?
I mean, what fun is blending in
with the crowd
when you're totally used to stan
Hmm.
Fine.
It's a good thing I always carry
an emergency make-up kit.
Ooh!
Way to go, Clover.
I don't even recognize myself.
Let's just solve this case
as quickly as possible
so we can go back
to our normal, much hotter selve
-It's officially time to call Je
-[beeping]
[gasps] He's not answering.
Forget Jerry.
Let's send a distress call to Ta
I know he'll save us.
[all] Help!
-Help us!
-[alarm blaring]
[gulps]
[chuckles]
[gasps]
Hello, Tad.
What's tickling your funny bone?
Oh, uh, nothing, sir.
I'm just enjoying being a WOOHP
and helping rid the world of evi
I see. You haven't heard from th
have you?
I'm growing very concerned about
Not a peep.
Strange. Well, if you do hear an
let me know immediately.
You have my word, Jerry.
Don't worry about those amateurs
I'll take care of them personall
[cackles]
Where could they be taking us?
I mean, this is outer space.
It's completely barren out here.
-Completely barren except for th
-Oh!
[all] Fabulous!
Okay, that does not look like
a very friendly place.
Get ready. I think we're about t
Fabulous!
No matter what kind of horrible
lurks behind that door,
I just want you guys to know one
[woman] Welcome to Fabutopia,
the newest frontier in Fabulizd
where all of your whims and dei
are catered to.
This place seriously rocks.
[woman] Enjoy our full-service s
sweatless gym,
air-conditioned indoor beach,
all-day nightclub,
and gourmet zero-calorie restar
Best of all, everything is cone
by luxurious, red-carpet-linedc
so you can strut in style froml
to location with utter panache.
[indistinct chatter]
So... this mission is about
people being transported
to a luxury hotel in outer space
Isn't it great? We should've bec
a whole lot sooner.
Guys, look. There's Peppy Wolfma
and Rob Heartthrob
playing beach volleyball togethe
[gasps] Whoa!
[grunts]
Fabulous!
[gasps] Not Rob too!
Now we have to find
the tasteless creep behind all o
[sighs]
Hello, Fabulites!
-Hey.
-I think we just did.
I am Fabu, your leader and savio
And this is our fabulous new hm
Fabutopia.
Wait a sec. I know this goofball
He's from the Top Ten Failed Mod
Of All Time Primetime Special.
[music playing]
[Alex] You're right.
Fabu was ranked number one
on account of his career
only lasted five minutes.
-[sneezes]
-[Alex] Literally.
-[crowd laughing]
-[cameras clicking]
You've all been summoned here
by my hood ornament beacon
which activated the hypnotizing
inside your cheek moles.
[all gasp]
I assure you
the journey was well worth it.
Fabutopia is exactly the type
of elite oasis
where people who look like us
deserve to live. [deep breath]
[all] Fabulous!
You see,
because my awkward childhood app
kept me out of the in-crowd,
I cultivated this perfect look
in an effort to become a famou
-But no one appreciated me...
-[man] All right, that's enough.
[cameras clicking]
...until now.
With all of you adopting
the Fabulized look,
I'm finally vindicated.
And I can blow up the Earth
and eliminate the non-fabulous.
[all gasp]
Blow up Earth? Are you completel
[crowd murmuring]
Uh, what I meant to say was... f
Blowing up our home planet sound
fabulous.
You are not fabulous. You are in
Then seize her.
Fabutopia is a guest-list-only v
-[grunts]
-[screaming]
Fabulous!
[gasping]
Hi-yah! [grunts]
[grunting]
Whoa!
[screaming]
-[groans]
-[snickers]
[gasps]
Let's get him.
Oh!
Hmm. [grunts]
[all] Huh?
[Yuri snickers]
Oh!
[gasps]
[groans]
[cackles] Trapped!
[evil laugh]
[Sam] Oh, no!
So, Yuri, how did a nice henchma
ever hook up
with a creepy uber-villain like
Vhen I vas cosmonaut,
Fabu helped me practice my space
[groans]
Fashionable valk very important
in Russian space program.
And, in return, Yuri was kind en
to build me Fabutopia and the Fa
Fad-ulizer is more like it.
I mean, hello!
Conformity is so three years ago
Yeah. 'Cause when everyone looks
beauty has no meaning.
Well, I don't care what you girl
which is why I'm not going to wa
my perfect look on you. [snicker
Then why are we strapped
into your freaky machines?
Because, with a few simple adjus
the Fabulizer can make you look
incredibly un-fabulous.
Un-fabulous?
Undateable. Unattractive times t
Hideous beyond your wildest drea
[gulps] On second thought,
why don't you go ahead and sign
for a lifetime Fabutopia members
I'm afraid it's too late for tha
[snickers]
Tell them ze rest
of your vicked plan, boss.
Ah, yes. After I give you
the ultimate bad-face day,
I'm going to launch you into spa
where you'll be stranded forever
You'll never get away with this.
Nice line, spy girl.
Now who's being "unoriginal," hm
[screaming]
[snickers]
[giggles] Fabulous.
Hmm.
-[gasps]
-[screaming]
-[yelling]
-[laughs]
[computer] Space capsule
propulsion system engaged.
-Ignition in five minutes.
-[timer beeping]
Enjoy your trip, spies.
[snickers]
[gasping]
This is all
that stupid sushi roll's fault.
I wish we'd never stopped it.
And I wish I didn't leave
the stupid house this morning
without a stupid eyebrow tweezer
What was I thinking?
[grunting]
How did our simple high school l
become such a mess?
I don't know. But at least
we all met and became friends.
Yeah. Even if it's only gonna la
a few more seconds.
Hello, agents.
-[all] Tad!
-Oh, how romantic!
You were crushin' on me so much
you simply had to come and save
[giggles] I mean, to save us.
-Hmm.
-[Tad laughs]
Save you? Ha! I don't think so.
But... you have to save us.
Yeah. We're, like, fellow spies.
Exactly my problem.
Until you three came along,
I was Jerry's number one agent.
Now you're in my way.
So I'm gonna let you get jettiso
and take credit for saving the d
[scoffs] I can't believe
someone who seemed so nice
could turn out to be such a lame
Naive much?
Apparently you've never heard
of a double agent.
-Farewell, ladies.
-[timer beeping]
[all gasp]
That's it. No more Miss Nice Spy
[grunting]
If only we could reach a gadget.
[gasps] I've got one.
[gulps]
[screaming]
-[line ringing]
-Come on, spies, answer.
Oh, I'll never be able to forgiv
if something terrible
has happened to those girls.
[chirps]
-Hmm?
-[beeping]
Hmm.
Huh?
Help!
My word!
Awesome!
Whoa!
-Clover!
-[grunts]
-[computer] Ignition canceled.
-[sighs]
Wow. Alex, you saved our lives.
That's what friends are for.
Now let's go stop Fabu.
I'm not saving anyone
until I get my face back.
It's time to go through
the un-Fabulizing process in rev
Now that's more like it.
Yeah!
Oh! Beautiful!
Just like your creator,
you're a thing of rare beauty.
[evil laughter]
It's a shame I have to blow you
-[Tad] Freeze, fashion boy.
-[gasps]
You may have outsmarted
those high school girls,
but you don't stand a chance
against a top agent like me.
[grunting] Ha!
Hi-yah!
Oh! Oh!
So, you're what passes
for a top agent these days?
I've seen more game
in a vegetarian restaurant.
Let's see how you deal with this
[grunting]
Take that.
[grunts] Yeah. Ha!
Missed me.
[grunting]
[snickers] Loser.
Not bad. Gadget time.
Whoa!
[grunting]
You look kinda tense.
How about a soothing
Fabutopia spa treatment?
-[snickers]
-[straining]
[grunting]
[groans] Hey. What's going on?
[laughs]
[gasps]
-[screams]
-[beeping]
Hold it right there, has-been.
There aren't gonna be any explos
on our watch.
-[gasping]
-Huh? You?
Wow, Tad, you're doin' a real ba
on the mission you hijacked from
I don't understand.
How did you girls escape?
Let's just say a gadget
is an agent's best friend.
Now get ready to have your butts
across the galaxy.
Hi-yah!
[grunting]
Take that.
[groaning]
Whoo-hoo!
Ha!
Nice touch. That's my kind of bo
The diamond's not for show, cupc
It's for boring into the Earth's
before it detonates.
-Hi-yah!
-[whimpers]
[grunts]
Yeah!
[grunting]
Try to get outta this one, trend
Nothing my 15% extra teeth can't
[screaming] Oh!
If I could still see, I'd imagin
Fabu's getting away right now.
[cackles]
[groaning]
-[timer beeping]
-[straining]
-[rumbling]
-[exclaims]
He's not the only thing about to
Help! I have an acute fear of be
to exploding projectiles.
[screaming]
Yes! Direct hit.
Whoa!
Sammy!
I mean, no! Bad idea!
[grunting]
Whether we like it or not,
looks like we're going for a rid
It's just as well,
'cause if we don't stop this thi
Earth's gonna be shattered
into a million pieces.
Earth? What about me?
Oh, puh-lease. You are so replac
Our planet isn't.
[screaming]
Here I am, facing my destiny,
close to the stars,
flying through outer space
like a shooting star.
My journey was short, but sparkl
[Clover] Hello! Over-dramatic mu
Huh? Who's there?
I've seen better acting on dayti
Good thing there are some real s
around to save your butt.
Look! There goes Fabu
in another one of his tricked-ou
Bye-bye, little spies. [laughs]
You gotta hand it to him.
He sure knows how to escape in s
Okay, forget Fabu.
We have to defuse this bomb.
What are you waiting for,
a written invitation? Hurry up.
I've heard about all I want to h
outta your pie hole for one day.
That control panel might be our
to shutting this thing down.
[grunts]
Whoa!
[screaming]
Okay, that was not the desired e
[Clover] We've got about half a
to figure this out
before we splat into Earth.
Hey, maybe we can use
the WOOHP Employee Manual to sto
Good thinking.
See if there's a chapter on bomb
[gasping]
Okay, either Jer hired a chimpan
to type this up,
or it's written in some kinda
weird WOOHP code.
Don't worry, guys.
I think we can still use it.
[screeching]
[all screaming]
Nice job, Alex.
Before this, the only book
that's ever saved my life
has been my little black book.
When you're done celebrating,
you might to check out
the collision course
you've just put us on.
[Sam] Oh, no!
Oops! What do we do now?
Uh... prepare for impact?
Hello, agents. Need a lift?
-Jerry?
-All aboard.
Hey! What about me?
Send us a postcard when you fina
to wherever you're going.
[Jerry] Ahem! Clover!
Ugh! Okay!
[grunts] Whoa!
-Ow!
-[laughs]
I'm not sure what kinda heat
you're packin' under the hood, J
but we gotta make it back to
the space station before that bo
Don't you worry about that.
We're packin' WOOHP power.
What? Hey!
-[gasping]
-Whoa!
Wow!
[screaming]
I have an idea.
Attention, all Fabulites.
You're in extreme danger.
Drop your umbrella drinks
and evacuate immediately!
[all] Fabulous! Fabulous!
Ugh! I think it's gonna take
more than a public service annou
to get through to these dimwits.
[gasps] You're right. We've got
take out Fabu's homing beacon.
What's going on?
One fabulous, decadent hood orna
-going down.
-Yay!
Huh? What?
-Oh!
-What's happening?
[indistinct conversations]
What are you losers doing here?
-[man] Look!
-[woman] Oh, no!
-[all panicking]
-Oh, no!
[screaming]
Everyone please proceed
to the WOOHP spaceship
in a calm, orderly fashion.
-[screaming]
-Help!
Wait, there's Oinky.
[sobbing]
[gasps]
Run, Oinky, run!
[squealing]
[whoops]
Wow! For a guy with really short
you sure can boogie.
-[snorting]
-[giggles]
[Sam] Come on, Alex, we have no
Speaking of boogieing,
it's time for us to bolt.
Floor it, Jerry.
Ooh, fireworks!
What a totally cute ending to ou
Our mission's not over yet.
We still need to catch Fabu.
And with all this extra cargo,
the spaceship is too slow to hel
You'll have to use your Jetpacks
[Clover] I don't suppose we have
a choice in the matter?
Of course not. Cheerio.
[screaming]
Whoa!
[Alex] The buddy system it is!
Awesome!
Okay, girls, time to blow this b
outta space.
Tornado-In-A-Can, don't fail us
Whoops.
Ha! Looks like my fabulous featu
have gotten away home free.
-[meows]
-Then again, maybe not.
[groaning]
[screaming]
[meowing]
-Huh?
-Sorry, Fabu,
but your Fabulizing days
are, like, so dunzo.
Not you again, pesky spies!
[girls laugh]
Congratulations on a job well do
Despite a few bumps in the road,
your first mission was a success
-Thanks, Jerry.
-It was, like, totally our pleas
Even if you did force us into it
I admit, there was a certain amo
of coercion on my part.
So if you don't wish to continue
I understand.
It's your choice.
Well, it's definitely been diffi
Mmm.
[gasps] But it's also been the m
exciting thing that's ever happe
And it's, like,
because of this whole spy thingy
that we met each other and becam
Yeah. So, if you're willing
to put up with us,
I guess we're willing to put up
Yeah, Jer, consider us WOOHPed f
It's a deal.
So what should we do
about all the Fabulized people?
Yeah. I mean,
as much as it would please Clove
we can't let Mandy know
we're secret agents.
It's no longer an issue.
WOOHP has erased their memories
and restored their faces.
Speaking of faces,
whatever happened to that totall
totally backstabbing Tad?
Tad is currently being disciplin
for his conduct
with the rest of our two-bit cri
in the WOOHP Containment Facilit
[grunts] Sorry, boss.
-[laughing]
-Ooh, that's just what he deserv
I wish all the dudes I'm mad at
could get the same treatment.
Speaking of dudes, allow me
to introduce you to Tad's replac
-Vincent.
-Ooh! I hope he's a babe.
Clover, didn't you learn your le
No office crushes.
[gasping]
Bonjour.
Wow! Hi there.
He's from our Paris office.
Looks like Sam's the only one
with excitement in her future.
-[Compowder ringing]
-Hello?
Hello, this is Peppy Wolfman.
I hear you have a pig that's bee
a traumatic experience.
I'd love to discuss it over lunc
[giggles] Awesome.
-[Compowder rings]
-Hello?
Hi, Clover. Rob Heartthrob here.
[Clover] No way.
Rumor has it you're a big fan
of my lyrical poetry.
How does dinner and a serenade s
[gasps] Hecka yes!
I guess all's well that ends wel
All may not be well at school.
I still need to see Mrs. Scritch
Well, in that case, you'd better
the quick way down. Cheerio.
[screaming]
[chuckles]
Just one of the joys of the job.
[bell ringing]
[panting]
Hurry up, you guys.
I'm gonna be late for my punishm
Excuse me, are you Samantha?
Yes, but I'm in a bit of rush.
I've got a date with detention.
Hmm. That doesn't sound like
the Sam I know.
In fact, I've just reviewed
your academic records
and was quite impressed.
And, as your new principal,
I look forward to having you
as one of my students.
Wow. Lucky break, Sammy.
Yeah. What are the odds?
About a zillion to one.
A coincidence like this
just screams WOOHP.
Good point. Which makes me wonde
what do you think happened
to Mrs. Scritch?
[wind whistling]
[shivering] H-Hello, students.
M-m-my name is...
[sneezing] M-M-Mrs. Scritch.
Huh! Guess we'll never know.
[horn plays "La Cucaracha"]
Ew! Oh, crud! I hate when there'
a squashed bug on my windshield.
Hey, newbies.
Wash and wax my whip, like, pron
No probs. I hope you like extra
-Whatevs! Just get it clean.
-[laughing]
-[gasps]
-Clover, what are you doing?
Getting Mandy back
when she least expects it...
with a little help
from the Pomade Grenade.
[screaming]
-[crowd cheering]
-[grunts]
-Huh?
-[chimes]
-[screaming]
-[explosion rumbles]
-No!
-[laughter]
Now that's what I call a "happy
-[Compowder ringing]
-[gasps]
Girls, I have an urgent missio
A giant lobster is attacking
the eastern coastline of Japan.
Uh, sounds really scary, Jer.
Unfortunately, I have an urgent
mani-pedi mission this afternoon
Yeah, and I have a ton
of schoolwork to do.
And I have to give Oinky a bath.
I'm afraid you leave me no choc
-Hmm.
-[helicopter hovering]
[gasping]
[all screaming]
Annoying much?
Well, look on the bright side, C
At least we're...
[all] Best friends forever! [gig
[music playing]
♪ All the gold and the guns in t
♪ Couldn't get you off♪
♪ All the gold and the guns
And the girls♪
♪ Couldn't get you off♪
♪ All the boys ♪
♪ All the choices in the world♪
♪ I remember when
We were gambling to win♪
♪ Everybody else said
Better luck next time♪
♪ I don't wanna bend
Let the bad girls bend♪
♪ I just wanna be your friend♪
♪ Is it ever gonna be enough?♪
♪ All the lace and the skin in t
♪ Couldn't get you off♪
♪ All the toys and the tools in
♪ All the noise ♪
♪ All the voices never stop♪
♪ I remember when
We were gambling to win♪
♪ Everybody else said
Better luck next time♪
♪ I don't wanna bend
Let the bad girls bend♪
♪ I just wanna be your friend
Why you giving me a hard time♪
♪ I remember when
We were gambling to win♪
♪ Everybody else said♪
♪ Is it ever gonna be enough?♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Ooh♪
♪ More and more, more and more
More and more, more and more♪
More and more♪
♪ Is it ever gonna be enough?♪
♪ More and more, more and more
More and more♪
♪ Is it ever gonna be enough?♪
♪ More and more, more and more
More and more♪
♪ Is it ever gonna be enough?♪
♪ More and more, more and more
More and more♪
♪ Is it ever gonna be enough?♪
♪ More and more, more and more
More and more♪
♪ Is it ever gonna be enough?♪